lancasterarchery.com 2019-07-06

# Lancaster Archery Supply Privacy Policy

### Effective Date: 05/24/2018

This Privacy Policy describes how Lancaster Archery Supply Inc. (“Lancaster Archery”, “we”, “our”, or “us”) collects, uses, and shares personal information of users of this website, [www.lancasterarchery.com](http://www.lancasterarchery.com/) or [www.lancasterarcherydealer.com](http://www.lancasterarcherydealer.com/) (the “Site”). We periodically update this Privacy Policy and reserve the right to change the provisions of this Policy or our privacy practices at any time. If you subscribe to Lancaster Archery, then you will receive notice when this Privacy Policy is modified. If not, then we encourage you to review this site periodically and we will alert you that changes have been made by updating the Effective Date of the Policy. Your use of the Site constitutes consent to any changes in this Policy as in effect on the date of such use.

#### Your Rights to Access Your Personal Information

You have the right to access personal information about you that Lancaster Archery has collected through this Site by sending a request for access to [support@lancasterarchery.com](mailto:support@lancasterarchery.com). You can also request that we correct or delete any such information by sending an email to the same address. To verify that the request is authentic, we may require that such request be sent from the email address associated with your personal information. While we will comply reasonably and promptly with your request, we may need to retain some of your information for our own record keeping or to fulfill a legal obligation.

If you are a subscriber to Lancaster Archery, you may correct, update, or remove your information by making the change on your user account settings page, or by emailing our Customer Support Team at [support@lancasterarchery.com](mailto:support@lancasterarchery.com). If you no longer desire our services, please contact us directly.

#### What is personal information?

Personal information means information that specifically identifies an individual person, such as name, mailing address, email address, phone number, or account number. It may also include other information about you, such as gender, date of birth, or other demographic information, or about your use of the Site, such as IP address or cookies, if that other information is linked to your personal information.

#### How your information is collected

Lancaster Archery collects personal information that you provide to us. For example:

  * If you sign up for Lancaster Archery’s services, Lancaster Archery may require you to register by providing your name, email address, phone number, and other information. You may be asked to create a username and password to login to our website.
  * If you apply for a job with Lancaster Archery, we may ask you to provide more detailed and sensitive personal information required for compliance with our hiring and equal opportunity policies and practices.
  * Our website includes social media features, such as links to our Facebook, YouTube and Twitter pages. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.
  * Our website also includes customer reviews where we may post information with your consent.

We also collect some of your information automatically when you visit or log on to this Site. For example, this Site collects your IP address and other online identifiers and records the pages that you visit and other information about your activity on the Site.

Like many other websites, we ask you to allow us to use “cookies” to remember information about you and improve your browsing experience on our Site. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our Site may be limited. We may also work with third-party providers who may use cookies on our Site. You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. For more information about cookies, including how to set your internet browser to reject cookies, please go to [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) or [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

#### What we do with your information

Lancaster Archery may use your personal information to:

  * provide products and services;
  * send requested product or service information;
  * send marketing communication;
  * send you emails or otherwise respond to questions, concerns, and customer support inquiries;
  * create demographic profiles of our subscribers, clients, and visitors to target our email alerts and website marketing; or
  * improve the services we offer you or the functionality of our Site.

Lancaster Archery does not sell personal information to third parties and does not transfer or share customers’ personal information. Lancaster Archery will share your personal information only:

With your consent;

  * to fulfill a legal obligation, including:
\- in response to lawful requests or legal process, including in response to law enforcement requirements; or  
\- as part of a business transaction, sale or transfer, or bankruptcy proceeding;  

  * for protection of personal or public safety or to prevent illegal activities;
  * to protect our own rights including enforcing our own policies, contracts, and terms of use.

Lancaster Archery may also use anonymous or pseudonymous personal information for internal purposes, such as to monitor the performance of its platform, or to track the effectiveness of and improve its products, processes, or services. Lancaster Archery may also share anonymous or pseudonymous data with selected third parties.

Note: We understand our emails may not always be relevant, for your convenience, an unsubscribe link is included at the bottom of each email. You may also manage your email preferences at any time by visiting http://www.lancasterarchery.com/preference-center.

#### How Lancaster Archery Protects Personal Information

Lancaster Archery follows generally accepted standards to protect personal information and information submitted by our customers, both during transmission and once we receive it. Lancaster Archery maintains all customers in carrier-class secure facilities protected by firewalls and other security devices. These measures are designed to protect visitor and customer information from loss, misuse, or unauthorized alteration. Lancaster Archery employs various information security mechanisms and internal policies and procedures to protect information from disclosure to unauthorized third parties. Lancaster Archery routinely audits its practices and policies to meet industry standards for data protection. Lancaster Archery provides an SSL encrypted, password-protected mechanism for logging in, viewing, uploading, and extracting customer data.

Personal information provided to Lancaster Archery by its customers remains the property of its customers.

#### Who to Contact

To report any issues or concerns, or to contact Lancaster Archery with any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, email us at [support@lancasterarchery.com](mailto:support@lancasterarchery.com), or call 800.829.7408.

You may also contact us as follows:  
Fax: 717.556.1390  
Postal Address: Lancaster Archery Supply, 21 Graybill Rd, Leola, PA 17540
